Que va-t-il advenir de moi désormais ?
Au bout d'un moment, j'ai arrêté d'y penser.
Peut-être ai-je simplement oublié...
...comment penser.
Plus rien ne change désormais.
Ce monde qui n'appartient qu'à moi,
continue jour après jour.
Mais je ne suis pas seule.
Cela ne me dérange pas du tout.
I could never find the right way to tell you,
have you noticed I've been gone?
Because I left behind the home that you made me,
but I will carry it along.
Mm, it's a long way forward,
so trust in me.
I'll give them shelter like you've done for me,
and I know I'm not alone,
you'll be watching over us.
Until you're gone.
When I'm older I'll be silent beside you,
I know words won't be enough.
And they won't need to know our names or our faces,
but they will carry on for us.
Mm, it's a long way forward,
so trust in me.
I'll give them shelter like you've done for me,
and I know I'm not alone,
you'll be watching over us.
Until you're gone.
Mm.
Mm, it's a long way forward,
trust in me.
I'll give them shelter like you've done for me,
and I know I'm not alone,
you'll be watching over us.
Until...
Même si ces souvenirs me rendent triste,
Je dois aller de l'avant, croire en l'avenir.
Même quand je prends conscience de ma solitude,
que je m'apprête à perdre tout espoir,
ces souvenirs me rendent plus forte.
Je ne suis pas seule...
grace à toi.