Got a firm grip?
Releasing evil skill formula.
Deployment prep complete.
Yuta, we have a green light. Go!
But slowly.
Sure, sure.
Hello, everyone!
I'm stuck in a nightmare.
Wait, wait! Time out!
You...
Henrietta, we got no flowers for you
Although you're husband may cut us
He's an animal, though everything is possible
Give us a kiss and maybe we can go out
It's hard to miss you when you follow us
about-out-out-out
Buy us some shoes and maybe take us for cola
We'll get you there in some filthy big gondola
And it's clean out the bank and
bump off your daddy
You can come live with us amongst
the has-beens and the addicts
These are crazy times down at Costello music
You can answer the phone and talk
anyway you choose it, come on
Clean out the bank and bump off your daddy
You can come live with us amongst
the has-beens and the addicts
These are crazy times down at Costello music
You can answer the phone and talk
anyway you choose it, come on
Good job!
Oh come on, oh come one
You understand, then?
You idiot!
Oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh
Seriously... What happened?!
You can open your eyes now.
The spring when I started middle school,
was when I got used to walking alone.
It truly is a lovely world.
No matter how many times I see it,
it always takes my breath away.
Does seeing your birth planet stir
up fond memories for you too?
Love is all, love is everyone
It is knowing? It is knowing?
But listen to the color of your dream
It is shining? It is shining?
A dry and barren land where no plants can grow.
Most of this world is part of the Land of Dusk.
Now, let the games begin.
Rippin' my heart was so easy, so easy
This is it. The moment I've been waiting for.
I will strike you down and pass through!
Let's end this duel before sunrise!
How does it feel now to watch it burn, burn, burn?
Just what is your motive anyway?
Our motive is...
...world domination!
Raise your weapon, raise your weapon
I'm just an ordinary high school student, y'know!
But I have to stop that thing falling from space!
Come on!
Raise your weapon
Okay, then.
Hang on tight!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Go!
Alright!
Rentaro, you're too quick to let your guard down.
Takeshi, behind you!
Trigger on!
Good!
Now, this is interesting!
You won't feel a thing, you won't feel a thing
Raise your weapon, raise your weapon
I'll tell you the story of how you and I met.
From the very beginning.
I'm not the same person I was before.
I chose you as my master.
I shall call you Shirou, then.
Don't expect too much.
Where is everyone?
I'm sorry, Hiyori.
Wait!
What's going on?
You'll be okay if we stay like this, right?
Enough is enough!
Unforgivable.
I'm home, Noel.
Apologize! Apologize to everyone!
Hey, somebody!
Stop it!
What can I do?
You bastard!
Stay away!
Don't cry.
I'm on your side.
You! This is all your fault!
And now, I'm holding Kou in my arms...
I'm sorry for being late.
Each week, your memories of those
you're close to reset, right?