Now, stop everything you're doing and look at me.
Looks like you've brought trouble again.
So, you want to serve the Oda family?
I play baseball to exist as an individual.
SCEPTER 4 has entered the building.
Prepare yourself!
They're coming.
Stop! Forbidden!
Is the world ordinary?
The world needs some action once in a while.
This next game should be interesting.
It's time for some piracy!
The scattering sweat shall turn into song.
The flowing tears shall turn into stars.
Dream.
I had a dream.
Until then, I have to be alone.
Right now, I cause others nothing but unhappiness.
I couldn't do anything!
He and I had something beautiful
but so dysfunctional, it couldn't last
Such pain as this
Shouldn't have to be experienced
I'm still reeling from the loss
Still a little bit delirious
Near to you, I am healing
but it's taking so long
though he's gone and you are wonderful
It's hard to move on
Yet, I'm better near to you
Yeah I'm better near to you
Ever since meeting you,
only good things have happened.
I'm so glad I met you,
that I could be with you.
Thank you.
Goodbye.
Ready, set...
I told you once
Ouh ouh, what do you do to your baby?
Ouh ouh, what do you do?
Ah ah, I'll be nearby when you lose her
Ah ha, I'll make her mine
Why do you treat her bad?
Why's that?
Ouh ouh ouh
I told you once, I told you twice
I wanna treat your baby nice
Ouh ouh ouh
I told you once, I told you twice
I'm gonna treat your baby nice
Ouh ouh ouh
I told you once, I told you twice
I'm gonna treat your baby nice
Ouh ouh ouh
I told you once, I told you twice
I'm gonna treat your baby nice
Ouh ouh ouh
I'm gonna treat your, I'm gonna treat your
I'm gonna treat your baby nice
See you later.
Special thanks to SSBDarren64, I will eatchu, and PennyRoyalty.