Three minutes to.
Is that a band?
Wait.
Lulubelle!
We got a baby, we can feast
We can dine three days at least
Baby blood and baby bones
Baby butter for the baby scones
Little baby feets, little baby toes
That's "sconns"!
Amazing.
Everyone of us wants the nose
No, it's not. What do we do?
Baby's had such very bad luck
Uh. Okay.
Now into baby we will tuck
Eat the baby, add some salt
Bayleaves, barley, powered malt
They're seasoning her.
Now baby's salted, she's a treat
Her destiny, it's time to meet
Baby we need
Baby we feed
Eat with our teeth
Better than beef
Baby so soft
Carried aloft
Big brown eyes
Oh, no.
Caramelise
-What?
-I wonder whose ship this is.
He's the Goblin King
Yes, the Goblin King
He's not a myth, he's an actual thing
Here's the King
Here's the King Goblin
We love the King, we sing ding-a-ling
Oh, my God.
And we love his chin when it's wobbling
He likes to dine on coincidence
What do I do? What do I do?
Leave her alone. Leave her alone!
It fills him, builds him up, and hence
He can eat
Five hundred puppies with golden fur
Orphan boys with jet-black hair
Circus clowns with the red balloon
He can eat me. He makes me swoon.
A banquet for a king on high
Oh, little baby
Say goodbye~~
Tough crowd.
Curtsy.
I'm the Doctor and this is my friend
Ruby Sunday.
And I would just like to say…
Why stop singing?
Rock it, Janice!
'Cause the Goblin King
Oh, the Goblin King
It's so good to meet you
You great, big thing
I can see you're having a fun day
Meet my friend, she's Ruby Sunday
It's good to meet you
Good to greet you
Good to say how diddly-deet you
It's my birthday - my, oh, my
I'm fifty miles up in the sky
But, Goblins, you can go to hell
'Cause you're not eating Lulubelle
Me and Rubes
We got just one hope
If I have understood that rope
'Cause stuck up there, when things got hot
I think I found the Master Knot
The Master Knot has been undone
That's when we start having fun
-Hold on tight.
-Wait, what are you do--
If you reverse intelligent gloves,
you get heavy.