Drop in straight out the coffin
Locked in, guess now you're all out of options
Watchmen, I'm a dark knight, no Gotham
Decimate your regiments, I'm tearing through your squadrons
Rotten, plead all your sins to Father
No caution, drown out the screams with laughter
No conscious, 'bout to go down like martyrs
And I'm burning up these Germans
like the Hindenburg Disaster
Gun to your head now there's no turning back
Dead or alive like a Schrodinger's cat
They be like "Nein" with a 9 in their mouth
And like Walter, I'm known for disposing the trash
Better witness, I'm a madman
It's like Christmas when I pack mags
Take a big ship and I crash land
It's like click-click, then it's bang-bang
You can't understand me like I'm abstract
Hear the twenty-one shots like it's blackjack
Fuck the Vatican, ain't one for backchat
I impale through the chest like I'm Vlad
damn
Cannot clap back, it's not happening
I'm a monster of God like I'm Anderson
I'm smiting these heathens, no Paladin
'Cause with the way that they fight me,
it's all so embarrassing
Whipping out my jackals so you know I bring the hounds
I'mma gun 'em down round
after round,
I'll be rounding them out, up the body count
I'll be leaving puddles on the battleground
Getting loud, I'll be striking on the clock like Big Ben
When in doubt I'mma up the ante like a pitch bend
Your life is in danger so major
The barrel is aimed like Auf Wiedersehen
Blood on my hands, blood on my shoes, blood in the
air
Blood on the ground, I'm on the move, better be
scared
Blood on my lips, blood on my drip, blood in my
lair
Enter the mists if you insist, I'll answer your
prayers
Blood on the walls, I'm unloading my shells
ifu、igyou、iyou、ijou
Terrifying, grotesque, bizarre, abnormal
Blood in the streets, hear the sound of the bells
yorisou wa yuukyuu no uta
Staying close with the time of eternity
London, this where the vampire dwells
seitou na sei to wa?
Just what is a proper life?
Blood in the city, so welcome to hell
jouki wo isshita choujou no choujou
The eccentric apex of paranormality
Rustage, Tophamhat-kyo
I speak Japanese, listen!
AYE gekkou no moto tatakae kyuuketsuki no sadame
The fate of a vampire is to battle in moonlight
fukafuka no fukai yuuka koji akeru omae no me
Soft, deep night wrenches eyes open
taiyou nado tou no mae ni atto iu mani obie
Men are terrified just before they ask of the sun
akutou nado dou narou to kyoumi nai
I don't give a shit what happens to villains
bakemono no shou chimimouryou mo nakashi
Proof of a monster bringing all manner of demons to tears
ito koushou na you shakume no kagayaki
A truly magnificent apparition with sparkling red eyes
AMEN Iscariot kono sekai ja houtei nado muryoku
Amen to Judas, in this world, laws have no power
touzen chikara to wa buryoku ni yoru shoumei
Of course, power is determined by force
WOOO
seimei he no houtoku、chiri wa soutou、kaimu na onjou
A blasphemy against life itself, sweeping up dust, bereft of remorse
SEARCH & DESTROY saa douzo
Search and Destroy, well, go ahead
kono me ni tsuienai emono nado nai
There's no prey that can escape me
kono go ni oyonde nige you nado tondemonai
We're this far in but you're still gonna run?
OOOOOH
moshi toori chi no goku made chi midoro irokoku natte
Literally all the way to hell, the blood I'm covered with gets darker
SLOW STARTER na shinasu no kimi
You're a slow starter but you just won't die
HURRY HURRY HURRY shosen asobi no karii ka ni
Hurry Hurry Hurry, in the end I'm just hunting for fun
choujinteki de arou ga muimi na hodo jinchi choueta
No matter how superhuman you are, I'm beyond human understanding
tagirasu jaki midakunrin suru yami kara
Overflowing with evil, when the crimson drips from the darkness I control, of course it's delicious yummy, no duh
shitataru kurenai no aji na ya YUMMY, NO DUH
shitawase kihin no aru COORDINATE jihi naki
A tongue-dragging coordinated fit, merciless
joui ha no chuuki wa utagaiyou mo nai hodokoku
My loyalty to the higher ups is undoutably viscous
Blood on my hands, blood on my shoes, blood in the
air
Blood on the ground, I'm on the move, better be
scared
Blood on my lips, blood on my drip, blood in my
lair
Enter the mists if you insist, I'll answer your
prayers
Blood on the walls, I'm unloading my shells
ifu、igyou、iyou、ijou
Terrifying, grotesque, bizarre, abnormal
Blood in the streets, hear the sound of the bells
yorisou wa yuukyuu no uta
Staying close with the time of eternity
London, this where the vampire dwells
seitou na sei to wa?
Just what is a proper life?
Blood in the city, so welcome to hell
I WONDER IF hito wa itarenai kyouchi
I wonder if there is a place prople cannot reach
Blood on the walls, I'm unloading my shells
ifu、igyou、iyou、ijou
Terrifying, grotesque, bizarre, abnormal
Blood in the streets, hear the sound of the bells
yorisou wa yuukyuu no uta
Staying close with the time of eternity
London, this where the vampire dwells
seitou na sei to wa?
Just what is a proper life?
Blood in the city, so welcome to hell
jouki wo isshita choujou no choujou
The eccentric apex of paranormality