You may know 'Dream'
Phantom like a shade turns up your heart
No way to grasp it which just fades
Mania and manic depressive come and go away
Your loneliness is the reason we could be born
Just in front of you
So if you have no love you can't see us
Quicksilvers sing
Prismrivers three sisters present
Just to bend sad reality
You may know matters you may not say
We just only can play fragile song
You may know Dream
Stepin' in the clouds just with the thunder chords
Dancin' all the time over the rainbow sounds
You may know Dream
Swingin' with the fog far away from your sane
Shankin' down your pain all by the rainbow sounds
You may know Dream
Which song do you love cool funny fine
Whatever you want, we can play
Just now, right now please order to play
We stand by you
Prismrivers three sisters present
Just to bend sad reality
You may know matters you may not say
We just only can play fragile song
You may know Dream
Stepin' in the clouds just with the thunder chords
Dancin' all the time over the rainbow sounds
You may know Dream
Swingin' with the fog far away from your sane
Shankin' down your pain all by the rainbow sounds
You may know Dream
Stepin' in the clouds just with the thunder chords
Dancin' all the time over the rainbow sounds
You may know Dream
Swingin' with the fog far away from your sane
Shankin' down your pain all by the rainbow sounds
You may know Dream
Karaoke par Touhou.net
Shankin' down your pain all by the rainbow sounds