Exactly one year since I lost my
son, but now I gain another.
I hereby christen thee, my robot son, Astro Boy!
From this day on, you live with
me in my house, understand?
Yes, sir.
And I'm going to be a
good father to you, to my son.
I'm going to teach you how to fly,
how to swim oceans,
how to leap over mountains,
how to be the bravest boy in the whole world.
I'll be proud of you, son.
Today, I finally got something that had
been bothering me off my chest.
The moment you back down is the moment you lose!
There's nowhere to run, is there?
So, I won't run away.
That's what I've decided.
If you insist...
...then let us fight until the end!
Here they come.
This time, I'll cut him to pieces.
When was the last time I felt scared?
You get to choose who's guilty.
Alright, I won't back down if you want to fight me.
I'm initiating aggressive maneuvers.
Understood.
Watch out!
Nice, Illya!
Let's go!
Enough funny business!
You won't escape this time!
Let's settle this.
Let's go.
If this is enough to beat them,
then it spells the end for humanity.
There are seven Rozen Maiden dolls. Seven sisters.
Impossible!
It's like love is on my mind!
Our love was lost
but now we've found it
And if you flash your heart, your heart
I won't deny it
I promise
That's why...
...I have to save her!
Aoi!
Shoko...
Our love was lost
Oh our love was lost
Lost, lost, lost, lost, lost, lost
Our love was lost
but now it's found
Well?
Will you be mine?
I look forward to working with you, Poem.
It's the start of a new era.
I'm happy you still come here to pay me company.
Would you like to try being an idol?
Your membership is approved!
Why are you looking again?
Boobs weigh heavier than one's life.
Pervert.
How do you figure?
Alright, let's go to the human world.
Well, I don't wanna wake up in the mornin'
but I've got to face the day
That's what all the friends
I do not like as much as you say
Kôsuke, I need your advice!
I'm not your brother.
But if you wanna come back it's alright, it's alright
It's alright if you wanna come back
Do you wanna come back? It's alright, it's alright
It's alright if you wanna come back to me
My, my.
We've created a troublesome situation.
I get the feeling it'll all work out.
Stop goofing around!
I'm taking this very seriously!
We're not done just yet!
You better believe it!
Start!
But if you wanna come back it's alright, it's alright
It's alright if you wanna come back
Do you wanna come back? It's alright, it's alright
Jeez. You idiot!
It's alright if you wanna come back
Do you wanna come back? It's alright, it's alright
This time, I blocked.
Who are you?
My name is Kudô Asuka.
Remember that from now on.
It's alright if you wanna come back to me
Special thanks to Taite
I love Japan!