Que vais-je devenir, à présent ?
Au bout d'un moment,
j'ai arrêté d'y penser.
Peut-être ai-je simplement oublié...
comment penser tout court.
Plus rien ne change.
Ce monde qui n'appartient qu'à moi,
continue jour après jour.
Mais je ne suis pas seule.
Ça ne me dérange pas.
I could never find the right way to tell you
Have you noticed I've been gone?
Cause I left behind the home that you made me
But I will carry it along
And it's a long way forward, so trust in me
I'll give them shelter like you've done for me
And I know, I'm not alone, you'll be watching over us
Until you're gone
When I'm older I'll be silent beside you
I know words won't be enough
And they won't need to know the names or our faces
But they will carry on for us
And it's a long way forward, so trust in me
I'll give them shelter like you've done for me
And I know, I'm not alone, you'll be watching over us
Until you're gone
Oh it's a long way forward, trust in me
I'll give them shelter like you've done for me
And I know, I'm not alone, you'll be watching over us
Until...
Même si ces souvenirs
me rendent triste...
Je dois aller de l'avant,
et croire en l'avenir.
Même si je me sens seule,
que je m'apprête à perdre
tout espoir,
ces souvenirs
me rendent plus forte.
Je ne suis pas seule...
grâce à toi.