Exact.
On prend quelles armes ?
Raquettes de tennis,
ballons de volley.
Et batailles de baffes.
Et démontages.
Doesn't seem to matter what I do
I'm always number two
No one knows how hard I tried, oh-oh
I, I have feelings that I can't explain
Drivin' me insane
All my life, been so polite
But I'll sleep alone tonight
'Cause I'm just Ken
Anywhere else I'd be a ten
Is it my destiny to live and die
a life of blonde fragility?
I'm just Ken
Where I see love, she sees a friend
What will it take for her to see
the man behind the tan
and fight for me?
On se retrouve
sur la plage de Malibu !
Chargez !
Que peux-tu, Ken ?
Tu peux, Ken
Et voilà, ils se détruisent.
Et si on réinstaurait
notre foutue Constitution ?
Super idée.
Quel nid de guêpes !
Surveillez les flancs !
Je suis touché.
- Impossible !
- Ils ont de vraies armes ?
Niet.
I wanna know what it's like to love
To be the real thing
Is it a crime?
Am I not hot when I'm in my feelings?
And is my moment finally here
or am I dreaming?
I'm no dreamer
Ken !
Can you feel the Kenergy?
They are, you are, we are...
I'm just Ken
Anywhere else I'd be a ten
Is it my destiny to live and die
a life of blonde fragility?
I'm just Ken
Where I see love, she sees a friend
What will it take for her to see
the man behind the tan
and fight for me?
I'm just Ken
(and I'm enough)
And I'm great at doing stuff
So, hey! Check me out
Yeah I'm just Ken
My name's Ken
(And so am I)
Put that manly hand in mine
So, hey! World, check me out
Yeah I'm just Ken
Baby, I'm just Ken