That, my liege, is how we know
the Earth to be banana-shaped.
This new learing amazes me, Sir Bedevere.
Explain again how sheep's bladders
may be employed to prevent earthquakes.
– Certainly, sir.
– Look, my liege.
– Camelot.
– It's only a model.
Knights, I bid you welcome
to your new home.
Let us ride to Camelot!
We're Knights of the Round Table
We dance whene'er we're able
We do routines and chorus scenes
With footwork impeccable
We dine well here in Camelot
We eat ham and jam and Spam a lot
We're Knights of the Round Table
Our shows are formidable
But many times
We're given rhymes
That are quite unsingable
We're opera mad in Camelot
We sing from the diaphragm a lot
In war we're tough and able
Quite indefatigable
Between our quests
We sequin vests
And impersonate Clark Gable
It's a busy life in Camelot
I have to push the pram a lot
No, on second thoughts,
let's not go to Camelot. It is a silly place.
Right.