Thanks for coming out
to my concert today, everyone!
-Stop looking, pervert!
-Sorry!
Living with a woman is tough, huh?
I hear you and Chitoge are just
pretending to be dating, aren't you?
That's wrong!
Well I'm so above you and it's plain to see
But I came to love you anyway-y-y-y-y-y
So you pulled my heart out
and I don't mind bleeding
Any old time you keep me waiting, waiting, waiting
Oh  Oh  Oh  Oh
I got a love that keeps me waiting
I'm a lonely boy, I'm a lonely boy
Oh  Oh  Oh  Oh
I got a love that keeps me waiting
And who are you?
Just someone who's a hero for fun.
Would you like to go on an adventure now?
Let's do this, then!
Oh  Oh  Oh  Oh
I got a love that keeps me waiting
I'm a lonely boy, I'm a lonely boy
Oh  Oh  Oh  Oh
I got a love that keeps me waiting
And so ends my last lecture.
You had ambition and drive,
and it was all of you that made the music.
Are you ready to amaze the audience?
Drink up every last drop and
shake off the feeling that you're watching me now
I should have just told the truth
It's just a fantasy, taking over like a disease
Pull me out of this I can't breath
It's burning through my chest
A fantasy, taking over like a disease
Pull me out of this I can't breath
I just need a rest from Paris
You know I held on too much
I left you at the station, I put you in my past
And now darling, all that shit's behind us
Never have to wonder, you never have to ask
You never have to
It's so ironic.
Since you've been gone, the old
memories keep coming back to me so vividly.
Welcome...
...to Fenrir, humankind's final fortress of defense.
We will now commence with the qualifying exam
for the Anti-Aragami Punitive Forces
known as God Eaters.
I'm the king of my own land
Creatures of my dreams, raise up and dance with me
This is the only way to save
everyone. Got it?
Then here we go!
Gatcha!
Now and forever
I'm your king
Time to turn this around...
...and raise hell!
Something dim and distant...
...fades into the hazy mist beyond.
These are memories I should've held onto,
but before I knew it, they were gone.