COUNTERACTION RISING
YEAH WE ARE READY FOR THE PUNCH LINE
THERE'S NO USE WITH ALL YOUR GIMMICKS
SO CHECK THIS OUT
LOGIN YOU DAMNED ONE'S
CRUSH THE WONT YOU COMPROMISE
THE NOISE COMES WE ARE READY TO BOW
WHAT ABOUT THE ANTIDOTE FOR THE JAMMED
AND HYPNOTIZED
REND THE LIE THAT COVERS
WHO'S THE REAL SUCKER NOW
sakimidareta hana no you ni
azayaka na itami daki
tatazumu machi wo nukete
mayoi no SERIF wa sute
kaeranai koe yo hibike
WE SAY WOW WOW WOW WOW
DATABASE DATABASE
JUST LIVING IN THE DATABASE WOW WOW
THE WALL OF PURE FICTION'S CRACKING
IN MY HEAD
AND THE ADDICTION OF MY WORLD
STILL SPREADS
IN THE DATABASE DATABASE
I'M STRUGGLING IN THE DATABASE WOW WOW
IT DOESN'T EVEN MATTER IF
THERE IS NO HOPE
AS THE MADNESS OF THE SYSTEM GROWS
DATABASE DATABASE
JUST LIVING IN THE DATABASE