Get back on track, it could be a payback
qsVY F5
lItTOrPz
You better break out before you black out
e  rZ r0 F
4DZISIQW
Back in black time to dust yourself off
ZPWQMVZU
84w5qq
Back in black time to dust yourself off
ZPWQMVZU
84w5qq
You gotta get paid, that's the way it is
m ZjMi
yt sqwo
Look inside you and see what your soul is
VAiZsOa
yzuhg2
Back in black time to dust yourself off
s ZjQi
sDStT  U
Back in black time to dust yourself off
s ZjQi
sDStT  U
No matter how hard I try I can't
ZiwuZ
eue  SLD
I see skies and I want you to paint it
ppxnva
IgFoyc
Back in black time to dust yourself off
ZiQMVZU
sxZdlf
You won't feel safe until I get away
iut syo
FZ3Ye
Everything melts the sunset slowly
rVk  i
yBtgD
Everything melts the sunset slowly
rVk  i
yBtgD
All alone
mo
h
I walk away like everyday somewhere out there
rsIx3s
ybitx
In my brain, I'm searching for the reason why I lose my mind
PYoWIDZ
fantAstiQue