ci = ; cn = _G.unicode.len(orgline.text_stripped)
function char_counter(ref) ci[ref] = ci[ref] + 1; return "" end
!char_counter(1)!!retime("start2syl",-1200+ci[1]/cn*100,-50)!
!retime("syl",-50,-50-$dur/4)!
!retime("postsyl",-50-$dur/4,($lstart + $send + ($dur/12)) < ($lend + 200) and $dur/12 or $lend - $lstart - $send + 200)!
!char_counter(1)!!retime("syl2end",$dur/12,200+(ci[1]/cn*100))!
Long ago somewhere in the future
In a place beyond space and time
There's a book for all to see
What has been, what could be, prophecies of the ages
Every little joy, every sorrow
Every little tear that is cried
Every word and deed every thought and feeling
All written there on the pages
Some embrace only shadow, some embrace the light
But the lives that we lead are the stories we leave
There in the Book of Life