RAISE YOUR FLAG
koe no kagiri
koe no kagiri sakende
kitto itsuka
itsuka dokoka
yume wo mitsuduke samayou
UNDER PRESSURE YOU ARE WAITING FOR DIRECTION
GOING ON THE ROAD WITHOUT YOUR MIND
ALL MISLEADS THEY GIVE IGNORING OUR DECISIONS
KILLING YOURSELF YOUR SOUL WE HAVE INSIDE
agakitsuduke taorekujike
haiagatte hashiritsudzukete
owari naki
yume no ma to ma
WE CAN STRUGGLE AND MUZZLE THE WORLD BEFORE IT FADES AWAY
RAISE YOUR FLAG
koe no kagiri
koe no kagiri sakende
kitto itsuka
itsuka dokoka
tadoritsuku to shinjite
COME ON AND RAISE YOUR FLAG
SO JUST RAISE YOUR FLAG
nando kujike mayoedo
iki no kagiri
tsudzuku kagiri