UNDER yurusu nara kyouhansha
“UNDER”
If you forgive this sin you’re as good as an accomplice
hitoribocchi ai wo choudai
I’m alone and lonely, please give me some love
UNDER nanika ga tarinainda
“UNDER”
I feel the emptiness inside me
motomeau kimari nantoka shitai FUTURE~
We agreed to seek each other,I wish we could do something about it,
Future
UNDER tsumi kara no kakurenbo
“UNDER”
I am playing hide and seek from the sin I committed
saa shippo maite damatte douzo
You should all give up and shut up
UNDER kowareta HEART motte
“UNDER”
I always have a broken heart
itai no wa itsu made tsuzuku no ka na
When will it stop aching?
ubaiai “doushite” no seishin kaibou
“Scramble for life”,
Dissecting our thoughts while asking “why”
machigai sagashi no enchousen wo
Looking for mistakes in overtime
dareka wo shitte ai de shibatte
You get to know them and then tie them with their EGO
sabakeru ka na?
Can you really judge them?
“kirai” tai “OK” no kyoukaisen wo
The border between “Hate” vs “OK”
wagamama no mama owatte ii no?
Is it really ok to be done with deciding with just your EGO?
subete wo shitta anata wa chanto
Will you be able to forgive them after listening to their sins?
yuruseru ka na?
UNDER dochira wo erabun da
“UNDER”
Which will you choose
damasareru hou ka damasu hou ka
To deceive or to be deceived
UNDER ataeru dake ja yaa yo
”UNDER”
I don’t just want to give
suru no mo sareru no mo ii mono
Both giving and receiving are good things
UNDER yume bakari miteirunda
“UNDER”
I keep on seeing dreams
mou hanpa bakka sukuenai na
I am always indecisive, I can’t be saved
UNDER shinjiru dake de ii no
“UNDER”
Just need to believe
yakusoku wo yaburu douri nado nai
There is no reason to break a promise
ubaiai “doushite” no seishin kaibou
“Scramble for life”,
Dissecting our thoughts while asking “why”
machigai sagashi no enchousen wo
Looking for mistakes in overtime
dareka wo shitte ai de shibatte
You get to know them and then tie them with their EGO
sabakeru ka na?
Can you really judge them?
“kirai” tai “OK” no kyoukaisen wo
The border between “Hate” vs “OK”
wagamama no mama owatte ii no?
Is it really ok to be done with deciding with just your EGO?
subete wo shitta anata wa chanto
Will you be able to forgive them after listening to their sins?
yuruseru ka na?
UNDER uso wo tsukanaide
“UNDER”
Don’t lie about me,
boku wa nani mo nai darou?
What did I do?
UNDER inochi wo tsukatte
“UNDER”
Dedicating my life
keshitai mono ga aru kara
There is something I want to remove
kuraiai haisha wa saki ni douzo
“Strife”
Losers go on first
machigaidarake no enzai datte
A false accusation full of mistakes
anata wa kitto egao de kitto
You would probably smile
yorokobu deshou
And be pleased
ubaiai “doushite” no seishin kaibou
“Scramble for life”,
Dissecting our thoughts while asking “why”
machigai sagashi no enchousen wo
Looking for mistakes in overtime
dareka wo shitte ai de shibatte
You get to know them and then tie them with their EGO
sabakeru ka na?
Can you really judge them?
“kirai” tai “OK” no kyoukaisen wo
The border between “Hate” vs “OK”
wagamama no mama owatte ii no?
Is it really ok to be done with deciding with just your EGO?
subete wo shitta anata wa chanto
Will you be able to forgive them after listening to their sins?
yuruseru ka na? ah~ ah~
damashiai kesenai UNDER~
Deceit, “UNDER” That cannot be removed