owaraseyou HARROW HARROW
Let’s end this!
“HARROW” “HARROW”
damatte tsuyosa ni naku natte
I can’t forgive the evil hurting the weak
yarusenai yarasenai
It’s unforgivable,
I won’t allow it,
watashi mou chikattanda
I sweared
dore kurai HARROW HARROW kuratte
How heavy
“HARROW” “HARROW”
dareka no yume ga iki wo tomerun nara
Is the damage to get in the way of someone’s dream
kono kiba de eguru yo
I’ll gouge you out with my fangs
sawatta kanjou wo kachi make wa dokoka
Stained emotions,
What is winning or losing
moe tsuki nai yori esa wo kuratte iru
Feeding on food so I don’t burn out
mata kura kura ni nari gucha gucha ni naru
Becoming light-headed again,
It all becomes crazy
motometa seichou ka?
The normalcy sought for,
iya iya ni nari shinde iku tabi
Fading away,
Everytime death comes
kokoro wa motto susunde iku
The soul moves forward
nikunde irunda
I hate all the evils in this world,
koware sou da yo
I feel like I’m about to break
tokutai agero hou i wo
The surrounding net covered with poison
owaraseyou HARROW HARROW
Let’s end this!
“HARROW” “HARROW”
damatte tsuyosa ni naku natte
I can’t forgive the evil hurting the weak
yarusenai yarasenai
It’s unforgivable,
I won’t allow it,
watashi mou chikattanda
I sweared
dore kurai HARROW HARROW kuratte
How heavy
“HARROW” “HARROW”
If it damaged someone’s dream to the points of stopping it
dareka no yume ga tomachatte chatten nara
kono kiba de eguru yo
I’ll gouge you out with my fangs
ata eta itami wo oshiete ageru
I’ll teach you the pain you caused
gomen ne oa iko nani wo megatten no?
It’s a tie after saying sorry?
What are you hoping for?
kawai sou na kodomo wa irekae masu ka
Shall we replace the poor soul,
aware na mousou mo
And the miserable delusion
waruginai kara mou shinai kara
“I didn’t mean to offend”,
“I won’t do it again”
dore dake katte kitan desu ka
How many wins in a row?
dare no sei da
Whose fault is it,
baka mitai da na
This is getting ridiculous
sawagi kata wa dou shiyou?
What should the punishment be
mitsuketai HARROW HARROW
Want to find
“HARROW” “HARROW”
kibatte okashiku nari sou da
I feel like I’m going crazy after straining my nerves
sukuenai dareka ga
The person that can’t be saved,
ima mo chou hoshikutte iku
Is now understanding the abnormality
dore kurai HARROW HARROW kuratte
How heavy
“HARROW” “HARROW”
If it damaged someone’s dream to the points of stopping it
dareka no yume ga tomachatte chatten nara
kono kiba de eguritai~
I want gouge you out with my fangs
umareta HARROW HARROW
Newly born
“HARROW” “HARROW”
kiratte ii deshou
It’s ok to dislike, right?
ushinatte ushimatte nani wo shitai sureba iinda
Losing it,
Losing it, losing it,
What should I hope for
oyasumi HARROW HARROW waratte
Goodnight
“HARROW” “HARROW”
watashi no koto suki ni nareru
Laugh and I can get to like myself
owaraseyou HARROW HARROW
Let’s end this!
“HARROW” “HARROW”
damatte tsuyosa ni naku nante
I can’t forgive the evil hurting the weak
yarusenai yarasenai
It’s unforgivable,
I won’t allow it,
watashi doushite mo yuzurenai no
I just can’t let it go
dore kurai HARROW HARROW kuratte
How heavy
“HARROW” “HARROW”
If it damaged someone’s dream to the points of stopping it
dareka no yume ga tomachatte chattenda yo
kono kiba de eguritai~
I want gouge you out with my fangs
tanoshisa ni oboetetai~
I want to be drowning in the knowledge that I am right