nanka hen da yo ne
I feel a little weird
mada narenai na
I’m still not used to feeling this way
kimi no koto ga ki ni nachatteru
I can’t get you out of my head
dare ni mo naisho ne
It’s a secret, ok?
nande iru no ka na
Why are you here?
sukoshi iya ni naru
You annoy me a little
umaku waraenaku nachatta no
I can’t smile well anymore
kimi no sei dakara
It’s because of you
ashita tte yasumi dakke?
What day is it tomorrow?
maa demo ikka asa wo mezashimasho
But I guess it doesn’t matter
Anyway, let’s be together till the morning
ohayo tte oyasumi tte
“Good morning”  “Good night”
nando datte aitaku naru yo ne
I want to be with you as many times as I can
futaribocchi chotto ii kanji
Just the two of us, I feel a little tingle inside
suki to suki ga LINK suru
Our love links us together
hitoribocchi satteiku ondo
Just me alone, the warmth starts fading away
yasashisa wo RELOAD shiyou
Let’s reload the warmth
fuuh, fuuh
dame na no ka na?
Am I a bad girl?
fuuh, fuuh
kotaenaide
Please don’t answer
fuuh, fuuh
nani shitai no?
What do you want to do?
fuuh, fuuh
oshiete hoshii
Please tell me
donna atashi nara
What type of girl do you like?
kimi wa suki desu ka?
nozomidoori ni nattemitai kedo
I want to become like that,
tabun muri dakara
But that’s probably too hard for me
kamiatte ataeatte
Play-biting each other, Warmth-giving each other
sore wa kitto suteki na koto da yo
That is probably an amazing thing
kore datte kimi ni totte
Even this makes you happy right?
shiawase tte ieru kotae desho?
I know you will respond that way
futaribocchi yatto mitsuketa no
Just the two of us  I finally found it
uso to uso de ENDLESS
The lies are endless
hitoribocchi yappa sabishii yo
Just me alone, it really is lonely
yasashisa wo RELOAD shiyou
Let’s reload the warmth
yachatta nda
I messed up
shichatta nda
I found out
yachatta nda
I messed up
shichatta nda
I found out
yachatta nda
I messed up
shichatta nda
I found out
yachatta nda
I messed up
shichatta nda
I found out
futaribocchi chotto ii kanji
Just the two of us, I feel a little tingle inside
suki to suki ga LINK suru
Our desire links us together
hitoribocchi satteiku ondo
Just me alone, the warmth starts fading away
yasashisa wo RELOAD shiyou
Let’s reload the warmth
futaribocchi yatto mitsuketa no
Just the two of us  I finally found it
uso to uso de ENDLESS
The lies are endless
hitoribocchi yappa sabishii yo
Just me alone, it really is lonely
yasashisa wo RELOAD shiyou
Let’s reload the warmth
fuuh, fuuh
dame na no ka na?
Are we over?
fuuh, fuuh
kotaenaide
Please don’t answer
fuuh, fuuh
nani shitai no?
What do you want to do?
fuuh, fuuh
oshiete hoshii
Please tell me
fuuh, fuuh
dame na no ka na?
kotaenaide
fuuh, fuuh
nani shitai no?