atashi ga ai wo kataru no nara
If I had thought, sought, to go express all my love,
sono me ni wa dou, utsuru?
how my friend would you look back at me then?
kotoba wa ari amaru bakari
These pointless words hurt and waste the time that we share,
muku no ne ga nagareteku
music sings so cleanly gracing the air
anata ga ai ni mamireru made
Until you’re pained, stained, from head to toe in your love,
sono iro wa maboroshi da
all the shades will fade away in the haze
hitoribocchi, oto ni nomarereba
The music shouts out alone and topples me down
zensekai kyoutsuu no kairaku sa
Fate itself just turns its head as it laughs at me now
tsumaranai bouzen ni oboreru
A hollow gaze, dazed, their life just ticking away
kurashi dare mo ga kare wo nazoru
The masses sing their praise and closely follow the same
kurikaesu tsukai mawashi no uta ni
It’s such a waste, shame, the music pours in my brain
mata mimi wo fusaida
An old tune that carries no weight
anata ga ai wo kataru no nara
If you had thought, sought, to go express all your love,
sore wo kotae to suru no?
then, my friend, is that a choice you’ll defend?
me wo tsubutta furi wo shiteru nara
Don’t close your eyes and lie, I’ll guide your hand to the light
kono kyoku de samashitekure!
I’ll sing and shout ‘til this life burns out I--
dare mo shiranu monogatari, omou bakari
I think and cherish that forgotten story, unknown are its glories
kowaresou na kurai ni dakishimete naki odotta
Moving close I grasp it just barely unbreaking through tears and the aching
misakai nai kanjouron yurusareru no naraba
If I could plead with all these empty emotions that just don’t mean a thing
nakidasu koto sura dekinai mama nomikondetta
With this old heart that seems on the verge of just breaking from all the aching
harisakete shimaisou na kokoro ga aru'tte koto
I couldn’t talk and just swallowed all of the words down, yes here once again--
sakebasete!
Just let me shout it!
sekai ga atashi wo koban demo ima
If my life is thrown away forgotten by the side,
ai no uta, utawasete kurenai kana
then could I here at the end sing of this love inside?
mou ikkai, dare mo shiranai sono omoi
One more time, would it be fine if I could try to find?
kono koe ni azuketemite mo ii kana
One last sign of life stuck in the voice that I had left behind?
anata ni wa boku ga mieru ka?
Look at me, can you see the one I try to be?
garakuta bakari nagetsuke rarete kita sono senaka
This fool that couldn’t take it
the aching, the garbage thrown there to their side, I hate it
soredemo suki to ieta nara
Through the pain if they still could love it all the same
soredemo suki wo negaetara
Through the pain if they wished to find love anyway
aa, atashi no zenbu ni sono imi wa aru to
Ah, maybe then it all was me, the days had all had meaning
wowaka
nee, ai wo kataru no nara
Hey, if you’re gunna share all your love,
ima sono mune ni wa dare ga iru
well then tell me my friend who will you meet at the end?
kokoro no hako wo koji akete
Stuck in a box, locked, I’ll free your heart with a knock
saa, ikiutsushi no anata misete?
Come you’re free, a fellow failure like me
atashi ga ai ni nareru no nara
If I could try, dye, myself the color of love,
ima sono iro wa nani iro da
come on tell me my friend just what hue was it then?
kodoku nante kigou de wa osamaranai
The pain of being alone hurts cause it never will show
shinzou wo kakaete ikitekitan da!
This heart’s a cage I built never knowing
DOPPEL modoki ga, soko ira ni afureta
Drowning in fakers from all of the aching
ageku no hate no kyou　LIE L-LIE LIE
but here at the end of life Lie L-Lie Lie
kokoro naki sore wo umidashita yatsura wa
All those who had left us here heartless and filled with fear
mikiri wo tsukete mou　BYE B-BYE BYE
threw it all to the side Bye B-Bye Bye
nokosareta anata ga, kono basho de ima de mo
The person who was by my side was left alone in here to die and
namida wo kotaeteru no doushite, doushite
try hard not to break or cry Oh Why Oh Why Oh
atashi wa shitteru wa, kono basho wa itsu de mo
That you had always stood to fight, protecting this place we hide
anata ni mamorarete kitatte koto!
there by my side!
itami nado amari ni mo narete shimatta
I’ve grown to take it, the pain welling in me, the breaking and hurting
nanzenkai to megurase tsuzuketa, kido to airaku
Joy, grief, rage, and pleasure, they all blend together, through every endeavor
ushinae nai yorokobi ga kono sekai ni aru naraba
If happiness that I cherish is real and is out there somewhere lost on this earth
tebanasu koto sura dekinai kanashimi sae atashi wa
Will I wander forever and ever in agony in this darkened and cold world
kono kokoro no naka tsuma hajiki ni shite shimau no ka?
As the blackned, the sheep that will never belong anywhere as I live forever?
sore wa, iya da!
Don’t leave me like that!
douyatte, kono sekai wo aiseru ka na
How could I grow to adore this world surrounding me?
itsu datte, korogari tsuzukerun darou
Tell me will I just keep on rolling on eternally?
nee, isso, dare mo kizukanai sono omoi
Hey I think I’ll take these feelings no one ever wants
kono uta de akashite miyou to 'moun da yo
Give this world a chance and share them all now with this final song
anata nara nani wo negau ka
Look at me, what exactly do you want to be?
anata nara nani wo nozomu ka
Look at me, can you tell me what you long to see?
kishin da kokoro ga dare yori ima wo ikite iru no
My heart breaks apart, however it still burns on now more than any other
anata ni wa boku ga mieru ka?
Look at me, can you see the one I try to be?
sore, atashi no yukusue wo terasu akari nan darou?
Is there light out piercing through the night, guiding me on to my life?
nee, ai wo sakebu no nara
Hey if you’re gunna shout out your love,
atashi wa koko ni iru yo
know that my friend, I’ll be here for you then
kotoba ga ari amaredo nao
These pointless words, hurt, but yet it never will stop
kono yume wa tsuzuiteku
Ever this dream will carry on and
atashi ga ai wo kataru no nara
If I had thought, sought, to go express all my love,
sono subete wa kono uta da
take my want and put it all in this song
dare mo shiranai kono monogatari
That story lost to all will be reborn now anew
mata kuchizusande shimatta mitai da
It seems that once again I’ll be humming the same tune