natsu no nioi ga shiteta
It smelled like summer
azemichi, hitotsu nyuudougumo
A footpath between rice fields, one gigantic column of clouds
yoru ga chikazuku made kyou wa aruite miyou yo
Until the night draws near, let's walk some more
tonari no machi no yomatsuri ni ikun da
To a night festival in the neighbouring town
nurui yoru, yuugatou no higurashi
A lukewarm night, cicadas in a light trap, humming, wind bells on the eaves of houses
hanauta, nokisaki no fuurin
sakamichi wo orita mukougawa
Looking up upon the hill road slope, longing for a dance
matsuri yatai no doukei
yoru ga chikazuku made kyou wa aruite miyou yo
Until the night draws near, let's walk some more
ue wo muite aruita, hana ga yozora ni saiteru
I walked with my head turned upward, flowers were blooming in the night sky
natsu no nioi ga shiteta
It smelled like summer
azemichi no zutto mukou he
To the other side of that footpath, always
dare hitori hito no inai machi wo sagasun da
Searching for a town with not a single person in it
nee, konna seikatsu wa gomen da
Listen, I don't want to live like this
sayounara, te wo furu kage hitotsu
Goodbye, a shadow of a waving hand, waiting for the night, a bus stop before my eyes
yoru machi, hanasaki no basutei
omoide no naka no fuukei wa
The scenery in my memories is absurdly beautiful, so
tsumaranu hodo kirei de
yoru ga chikazuku made kyou mo aruite itan da
Until the night drew near, I walked today as well
mabuta wo tojireba mieru, natsu no nioi ga suru
I see it when I close my eyes, it smells of summer
saa, motto tooku ikou yo
Come, let's go farther
saa, motto nigete ikou ze
Come, let's run away from here
saa, bokura tsumaranai koto wa zenbu houttoite
Come, let us ignore all the unimportant things
michi no mukou he
To the other side of the road
natsu no nioi ga shiteta
It smelled like summer
azemichi, hitotsu nyuudougumo
A footpath between rice fields, one gigantic column of clouds
dare hitori hito no inai machi de kizukun da
In a town with not a single person in it I finally notice
kimi mo inai koto ni yatto
That you're not there either
nurui yoru, yuugatou no higurashi
A lukewarm night, cicadas in a light trap, humming, wind bells on the eaves of houses
hanauta, nokisaki no fuurin
sakamichi wo orita mukougawa
Looking up upon the hill road slope, longing for a dance
matsuri yatai no doukei
otona ni natte mo zutto oboeteru kara
Even after growing up I will always remember these things
nee tooku he ikou yo, ano oka no mukou he
So, hey, let's go far away from here, beyond that hill
saa, motto tooku ikou yo
Come, let's go farther
saa, motto nigete ikou ze
Come, let's run away from here
saa, bokura tsumaranai koto wa zenbu houttoite
Come, let us ignore all the unimportant things
michi no mukou he
To the other side of the road