(bakkoi!)
(Batta Swing!)
(onsha!)
(Yoohoo!)
pane tte chouchou shinu tte
Way, totes to die for,
Gensōkyō ukeru-NATIC
Gensokyo Ridiculunatic
samo HUNG arinaan teka
Sammo Hung! Maybe, um
go-zaru de gozaru de
goza mori GOMEZ
It's a pile of seats of being monkeys, Gomez.
panchira de chouchou ganmi de
Panty flash, Totes staring,
hanninzou shuzai de chekira
Criminal profile, Check it out by interview,
ganmen uzamen
A face, an inyoface.
sorya majidarubisshu~
That's whatevs.
tokusoubu dashinuite
Scooping the S.I. department,In a photo I got,
te ni ireta shashin ni wa
nazo wo yobu akai moji
Red letters inviting mystery:A warning of murder.
satsugai no yokoku
jiken kita━━━━(ﾟ∀ﾟ)━━━━!!
Case is here!
(bakkoi!)
jiken OK
Case, ok
(bakkoi!)
VIVA jiken
¡Viva el case!
(bakkoi!)
giza jiken
Spiky case
(bakkoi!)
jiken ↑age↑
Case bump
(bakkoi!)
jiken NOW
Case rn
(bakkoi!)
san-do no meshi yori
jiken ga meshiuma
Case, like schadenfreude, tastes better than dinner!
COME ON!!
G.J.!!
shitai! shitai yo!
Corpse! Yes, a corpse!
mune ni SPELLCA' sasatteru wa
A spellcard is stuck in her chest.
dou mite mo tasatsu
By all appearances, a homicide
toriaezu genba no
Right away I snap a candid of the scene
shashin wo gekisha
suiri! suiri yo!
Inference! Yes, an inference!
shinjitsu wo miyaburu
I see right through to the truth.
shouko wa juubun
I have enough evidence.
ALIBI wo kuzushite sengen
A declaration to destroy your alibi, Shameimaru:
Shameimaru
jien otsu!
Grats, you played yourself!
PAPARAZZI PAPARAZZI
PA-PAPARAZZI PAPARAZZI