Mou sugu tokei wa roku-ji
The time's almost six
Mou soko ni ichiban boshi
The evening star's already out there
Kage wo funde yoru ni magiretaku naru kaerimichi
Walking home, stepping on shadows
I'm hoping to blend into the night
Yeah, something's not right.
Iina kimi wa minna kara aisarete
Lucky you, lucky you
It's been fine this whole time,
Must be nice to have everyone love you
but now I can't get the E string in tune...
"Iiya boku wa zutto hitori kirisa"
"No, I've always been alone."
Kimi to atsumatte seiza ni naretara
If only I could become
a constellation with you...
Hoshi furu yoru isshun no negaigoto
On a night of falling stars,
I make that moment's wish
The E string!
Not good...
But if I can at least get
the B string in tune...
Kirameite yurameite furueteru signal
A sparkling, twinkling,
trembling signal up high
The peg's broken!
She can't use the B string now.
Kimi to atsumatte seiza ni naretara
She won't be able to do her solo.
If only I could become
a constellation with you...
What'll I do?
Sora miagete yubi wo sasareru you na
My solo's coming up...
The kind that people point to in the sky
If our big culture festival performance
fails because I had equipment trouble...
Tsunaida sen hodokanaide
Don't let these lines
that link us come undone
What do I do?
What do I do, what do I do,
what do I do, what do I do?!
Boku ga donna ni mabushikute mo
No matter how brightly I shine
Kita-san...
She's ad-libbing completely on the fly!
I'm going to make sure everyone can see...
how amazingly cool Gotoh-san really is!
What's their guitarist doing?
Dunno, but it's pretty awesome!
Who whips out the bottleneck
playing at a time like this?
Now it won't matter
if she's a little out of tune!
Haruka kanata bokura wa deatte shimatta
We met each other, so far away
Karma dakara nan domo deatte shimau yo
And because it's our karma,
we'll meet again and again
Kumo no sukima de
In the gaps between the clouds
Kimi to atsumatte seiza ni naretara
If only I could become
a constellation with you...
Yoru hirogete egakou esoragoto
As night falls, I dream that unlikely dream
Kurayami wo terasu you na mangetsu janakute mo
Not quite a full moon
But still lighting up the dark
Dakara atsumatte seiza ni naritai
I want to become a constellation with you
Irotoridori no hikari hanatsu you na
The kind that puts out many-colored light
Tsunaida sen hodokanai yo
I won't let these lines
that link us come undone
Kimi ga donna ni mabushikute mo
No matter how brightly you shine