ame ga futta hana ga chitta
The rain and flower petals fell
tada somatta hoho wo omotta
I only imagined your blushing cheeks
boku wa zutto baketsu ippai no gekkou wo nonderu
I'm always drinking a bucket full of moonlight
hontou nan da yoru mitai de
Really, it tastes like the night
usuku toumei na kuchizawari de
A weak, transparent taste
sou nan da, tte waratte mo ii kedo
I don't mind if you smile and reply "is that so," though
boku wa kimi wo matteiru
I'm waiting for you
natsu ga satta machi wa shizuka
After summer ends, the town is quiet
boku wa yatto heya ni modotte
I finally got back into my room
yoru ni natta
Night came,
konna yoi tsuki wo hitori de miteru
And I'm admiring such a beautiful moon alone
hontou nan da, mukashi no boku wa namida ga houseki de dekitetan da
Really, my tears were made of gems back then
sou nan da, tte waratte mo ii kedo
I don't mind if you smile and reply "is that so," though
koe wa mou tokkuni wasureta
I've forgotten your voice long ago
omoide mo ai mo shinda
Both the memories and the love inside me have died
kaze no nai umibe wo aruita ano natsu e
I'm heading toward that summer, when we walked the beach where the wind doesn't blow
boku wa sayonara ga hoshiin da
I want to hear you say goodbye
tada madoromu you na
I can't even say a word,
mono hitotsu sae iwanai mama
As if I'm just falling into a slumber
boku wa kimi wo matteiru
And, like that, I'm waiting for you
toshi wo totta hitotsu totta
I grew older by a year
nanimo nai heya de haru ni natta
Then, spring arrived to greet this empy room
boku wa ai wo, soko ga nuketa hishaku de nonderu
I'm drinking love, by scooping it up with a bottomless ladle
hontou nan da aji mo shinakute
Really, it's bland
nomeba nomu hodo nodo ga kawaite
and I get thirstier the more I drink it
sou nan da, tte waratte mo ii kedo
I don't mind if you smile and reply "is that so," though
boku wa yoru wo matteiru
I'm waiting for the night
kimi no hanauta ga hoshiin da
I want to hear your humming
tada madoromu you na
I can't even say a word,
mono hitotsu sae iwanai mama
As if I'm just falling into a slumber
boku wa kimi wo matteiru
And, like that, I'm waiting for you
kimi no me wo oboete inai
I don't remember how your eyes looks like
kimi no kuchi wo egaite inai
I'm not drawing the shape of your mouth
mono hitotsu sae iwanai mama
I can't even say a word
boku wa kimi wo matteinai
And nor am I waiting for you
kimi no hana wo shitte inai
I don't recognize your nose
kimi no hoho wo omotte inai
I'm not imagining your cheeks
sayonara sura iwanai mama
Even "goodbye" remains unsaid
kimi wa yoru ni natte yuku
And, like that, you're becoming the night