waraetara, modoreta nara
If I could laugh,
If I could go back
ikita mama shinda furi shiteirun darou?
I’d play dead even though I’m alive right?
owaretara, tomareta nara
If I could end,
If I could stop
kono yume wa itsumade tsuzukun darou
How long would this dream go on?
tamekonde kakusanakute ii
You don’t have to keep it in and hide it away
boku ga boku wo sukutte agemashou
“I” will save “me”
dakiatte kyou wa oyasumi
Snuggle together and say “Good night”
kawaribanko nou wo yurase~
Switch,
Shake up that brain
nande boku ga koko ni iru no
Why am I here?
machigai janai no?
It must be a mistake?
sou da boku wo tashikamete yo
Take a good look at me
chanto mitsukeru made~
Until you find me
kitto hontou ga wakaru yo
The truth will come to reveal itself
uso nara kimi no koto yurusanai yo
I won’t forgive you if this is happening to me even though I’m right
kowasetara, hen wareta nara
If I could break it,
If I could change
dekiru ka na itsukara akirametetan darou
Can I do it,
I wonder from when I started to gave up
nakusetara, erabeta nara
If I could lose it,
If I could choose
wagamama ka na kore kurai wa ii deshou?
Is this selfish?
This isn’t too much is it?
nomikonda MINUS no IMAGE ga
The minus energy that I swallowed
boku wo dakishimetekureta no
Hugged me
ikiyou toshite ii janai ka
Maybe it’s ok to try to keep on living
hanbunko kodou wo narase~
Split in half,
Make that heart beat
nande boku ga koko ni iru no
Why am I here?
machigai janai no?
It must be a mistake?
sou da boku wo tashikamete yo
Take a good look at me
chanto mitsukeru made~
Until you find me
kitto hontou ga wakaru yo
The truth will come to reveal itself
uso nara kimi no koto yurusanai yo
I will NEVER forgive you if this is happening to me even though I’m right
sonna arienai kotoba bakka
All those ridiculous accusations
kizu wo tsukete osaetsuke
Hurting it,
Holding it down,
kawaranain da ne
It doesn’t change anything, does it
aa doko ni ite mo kou da
Ahhh,
It’s the same anywhere I go
machigai ga machigai janai mitai~
It’s like what’s wrong isn’t wrong
isso boku ga mou nisemono~
I’m already the fake one
kitto boku wa warukunai yo
I’m probably not to blame,
nani mo nain da
It’s probably nothing
kitto warui yume wo miteru
I’m probably just having a bad dream,
hayaku okinaku cha
I need to wake up soon
nande boku ga koko ni iru no
Why am I here?
machigai janai no?
It must be a mistake right?
sou da boku wo tashikamete yo
Take a good look at me
chanto mitsukete yo
Until you find me
nande nee nande
Why,
Hey why,
doko ni mo boku wa inai na
I’m nowhere to be found
dakara uso nara kimi no koto yurusanai yo
So
I will NEVER forgive you if this is happening to me even though I’m right
nande nee nande
Why,
Hey why,
koko kara dashite kudasai
Please let me out of here
dou ka machigai da to
Please tell me it’s a mistake, that’s it’s a lie
uso da yo to itte
boku ga tadashii to
That I’m right,
ima nara kimi wo yurushite ageru
I’ll forgive you If you tell me now