doushite hanareteku no?
Tell me, why are you drifting away from me?
nee doushite boku no sei na no?
Tell me, why do you say it’s my fault?
iou to shita kotoba ga
The word I tried to say was “You’re unfair”,
“hikyou da ne” tte boku wo warau
And those words thought how pitiful I am
doushite kowareteku no?
Why is it breaking?
nee doushite kawaranaide yo
Tell me why? Please don’t change
iou toshite yametara
If I tried and couldn’t say it,
“dame da ne” tte okoru kuse ni
You would get angry at me and say “You’re hopeless.”
daredemo dekiru koto boku ni mo dekitara na
If only I could do what anyone else could do
chigatteta hazu no mirai wa
The right future unfairly chose the wrong me
fubyoudou ni koi wo shita
himei wo shiteita, himei wo shiteita
I cried, I screamed
aisareru jakusha ni naritakatta
I wanted to be a pitied and loved weakling
hitei wo shiteita, hitei wo shiteita
I was in denial, I was in denial
doushitemo tashikamete mitakatta
I just had to make sure
aHaHA, boku ni kizuite
AHahA Please notice me
aHaHA, dareka kizuite yo
aHaHA Someone please notice me...
machigatteita no wa boku datta
I was wrong
sou, boku datta nda
Yes, it was me
ii yo boku no sei da
It’s fine,
It’s all my fault right?
mou ii yo hazure dakara
It’s enough, I am a “disappointment”
kinou wo kurikaeshite akiramette daiji dakedo
I am always repeating yesterday,
Though it’s important to know when to give up
ii yo yokunai kedo
It’s fine,
Though it’s really not
mou ii yo omottenai kedo
It’s really fine, though I don’t really think so
shirou to shita tokoro de
When I tried to understand it,
mata iya tte kao wo suru nara
You’ll make that disappointed face again
kurutteru tte hometekureta
You praised me by saying “You’re crazy.”
arigatou ganbaru yo
Thank you, I’ll do my best
dore kurai tsuzuketara
How many more times do I have to do this so I can be human?
boku wa hito ni nareru?
gisei wo shiteita, gisei wo shiteita
I’ve become a victim, I’ve become a victim
boku no kodoku wa nozomareteita nda
My loneliness was desired
kakou wo shiteita, kakou wo shiteita
I was falling, I was falling down
START ichi ga chigau mama hajimatta
My life started in a wrong spot
aHaHA, boku ni kizuite
AHahA Please notice me
aHaHA, dareka kizuite yo
aHaHA Someone please notice me...
machigatteita no wa boku datta
I was wrong
sou, boku datta nda
Yes, it was me
hitotsu futatsu kasaneta tte
Even if I keep trying it,
mata sugu kuzusarete
It’s broken right away
inai mono iranai mono dokoka de ikiteru no?
The things that aren’t here, and the unneeded things
Is it still living somewhere?
himei wo shiteita, himei wo shiteita
I cried, I screamed
aisareru jakusha ni naritakatta
I wanted to be a pitied and loved weakling
hitei wo shiteita, hitei wo shiteita
I was in denial, I was in denial
doushitemo tashikamete mitakatta
I just had to make sure
gisei wo shiteita, gisei wo shiteita
I’ve become a victim, I’ve become a victim
boku no kodoku wa nozomareteita nda
My loneliness was desired
kakou wo shiteita, kakou wo shiteita
I was falling, I was falling down
START ichi ga chigau mama hajimatta
My life started in a wrong spot
aHaHA, boku ni kizuite
AHahA Please notice me
aHaHA, dareka kizuite yo
aHaHA Someone please notice me...
machigatteita no wa boku datta
I was wrong
sou, boku datta
Yes, it was me
aHaHA, boku ni kizuite
AHahA Please notice me
aHaHA, dareka kizuite yo
aHaHA Someone please notice me...
machigatteita no wa boku datta
I was wrong
sou, boku datta nda
Yes, it was me